[Music]
Hey, stop the vehicle, stop, stop, stop,
why are you, three people riding without helmet, a
challan of ₹2000 will be issued. Hey Sir, leave it, this is a staff vehicle, there is no staff, I know very well that you will be fined, okay, I will get you to talk to any SP, DSP, Collector, I will not let your vehicle go without a challan,
now wait, just wait for
a minute.
[Music]
Hi, Inspector Robin Jindal ji has
seized my vehicle, please talk to him once.
Hello who?
Yes madam.
No no madam, I am leaving now.  I am
leaving now.  Sorry madam, sorry.
Wow, that's a lot of recognition.  Which
minister did you make me talk to?
Hey, he's my brother.
I made him talk to his wife and my sister-in-law.
[music]